The William Siegmann Collection, 1932-2007 IULC038 IULC038
Liberian Collections
- Subject Files
  - Conferences and Meetings
    - Liberian Studies Association 21st Annual Conference, 1989 (Box 28)
    - Liberian Studies Association 28th Annual Conference, 1996 (Box 28)
  - Cultural Heritage of Nimba County Presented at the 125th Independence Day Celebration, 1972 (Box 28)
  - Friends of Liberia, 1991-1999 (Box 28)
  - Friends of Liberia Election Monitoring Project, 1997 (Box 28)
  - Government
    - Acts Passed by the Legislature of the Republic of Liberia During the Session 1954-1955 (Box 28)
    - An Act to Provide an Internal Revenue Code of the Republic of Liberia Approved December 11, 1937, 1957 (Box 28)
    - Annual Messages, 1909-1921 (Box 28)
  - Humanities Projects in Media, 1984 (Box 28)
  - Liberia Centennial Materials, 1947 (Box 28)
  - Liberian Rice Riots, undated, 1979-1980 (Box 28)
  - Programs, undated, 1966-1988 (Box 28)
  - St. Petersburg Newspapers, 1995 (Box 28)
  - Tubman Center of African Culture, 1970 (Box 28)
  - Tubman Memorial, undated (Box 28)
  - U.S. Consuls and Ministers Dispatches, undated (Box 28)
- Teaching
  - Art and Society Syllabus, 1978 (Box 28)
  - Cuttington College
    - Administration, 1975 (Box 28)
    - African Studies Program, undated, 1975-1976 (Box 28)
    - Africana Museum, undated (Box 28)
    - Africana Museum Annual Report, 1969-1971 (Box 28)
    - Annual Reports, 1967-1973 (Box 28)
    - Commencement Program, 1967 (Box 28)
    - "Cuttington at the Crossroads", 1974 (Box 28)
    - Cuttington College Yearbook, 1974 (Box 28)
    - Docent Training, undated (Box 28)
    - Faculty Handbook, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
    - Homecoming, 1972 (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965-1994 (Box 28)
    - Newsletter, 1969 (Box 28)
    - "Personal Reference for Student's Record" Form, 1974 (Box 28)
    - Political Criticims Statement, 1968 (Box 28)
    - Que Circa Newsletter, 1972-1973 (Box 28)
    - Souvenir Programs, 1974-1994 (Box 28)
    - Survey, 1974 (Box 28)
    - "The Vanguard" Newsletter, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Freetown Community, undated (Box 28)
  - Indiana University, undated, 1977 (Box 28)
  - Student Writings
    - "The Barroba Kwi Society", undated (Box 28)
    - "Bibliography Music and Dance in Liberia and Sierra Leone", 1972 (Box 28)
    - "The Grebo Mask Dance or Ceremonial Mask Dance", undated (Box 28)
    - "Kissi Masks", undated (Box 28)
    - "Masks Among the Gbunde", 1975 (Box 28)
    - "The Meaning of African Sculpture", 1974 (Box 28)
    - "Producing Country Cloth in the Mano Area", 1974 (Box 28)
    - "The Traditional Political System of the Kpelle People", 1968 (Box 28)
- Writings
  - Bassa Men's Societies, 1968 (Box 28)
  - Clan and Chiefdom Maps of Grand Bassa County and Marshall and River Cess Territories, 1976-1977 (Box 28)
  - Clan and Chiefdom Maps - Liberia Map, Counties, District, Clans, and Townships, undated (Box 28)
  - Clan and Chiefdom Maps - Raw Data, undated (Box 28)
  - Clan and Chiefdom Maps - Raw Data and Notes, undated (Box 28)
  - Clan and Chiefdom Maps - Types of Bassa and Names for other Tribes, undated (Box 28)
  - Drafts
    - Art and Social History, undated (Box 28)
    - Bassa, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Bassa (Chapter I), undated (Box 28)
    - Bassa (Chapter II), undated (Box 28)
    - Bassa Cove, undated (Box 28)
    - Bassa Masks, undated (Box 28)
    - Classification of Kruan Languages, 1982 (Box 28)
    - Djenne Sales - Notes and Drafts, undated (Box 28)
    - Earliest Economic Activities, undated (Box 28)
    - Early Sources on the Malagueta Coast to 1750 - Annotated Bibliography (Box 28)
    - Edina, Hartford, Fortsville, undated (Box 28)
    - European Involvement in the Malaguetta Coast, undated, 1971 (Box 28)
      4 folders
    - Junk River and Marshall, undated (Box 28)
    - Kissi, undated (Box 28)
    - Liberia,, undated, 1968 (Box 28)
    - Liberian Archaeology/Prehistory, undated (Box 28)
    - Liberian Men's Dress, undated (Box 28)
    - Little Bassa, undated (Box 28)
    - Mano Masks, undated (Box 28)
    - Mel and West Atlantic - Notes, undated (Box 28)
    - National Archives of Liberia, undated (Box 28)
    - Poro, undated (Box 28)
    - Port Cresson - Boyer Grander - 1852, undated (Box 28)
    - A Short Historical Record of Tabacconi, undated (Box 28)
    - Some Functions of the Bundu Mask in Western Liberia and Sierra Leone, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Spirit Manifestation and the Poro, 1977 (Box 28)
    - Style and Ethnicity Drafts, undated (Box 28)
  - East Guinea Coast, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Ethnographic Survey of Southeast Liberia - Report on the Bassa, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Joel Chandler Harris and Negro Fiction in the New South, undated (Box 28)
  - Kpelle Clan and Chiefdom Maps, 1982 (Box 28)
  - Liberian Masks - Annotated Bibliography, undated (Box 28)
  - Men's Masquerades of Sierra Leone and Liberia, 1976-1980 (Box 28)
  - National Museum Monrovia, 1974 (Box 28)
  - North and West Guinea Coast, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Patchwork Gowns as State Regalia in Western Liberia,, undated, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Preliminary Proposal for The Establishment of a Museum of Liberian Arts and Crafts at Bong Mines Inc., 1968 (Box 28)
  - Rock of the Ancestors,, undated, 1977-1978 (Box 28)
    4 folders, including comments by Arthur Abraham, addendum, and reviews
  - Spirit Manifestation and the Poro, 1980 (Box 28)
  - Spirits, Men and Masks, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Tribal Distribution on the Malaguetta Coast, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 28)
  - Visions of Africa, 1994 (Box 28)